Toni Morrison Papers, 1957-: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
Toni Morrison Papers
1970-2015
1929-2015
C1491
Princeton University. Library. Dept. of Rare Books and Special Collections Manuscripts Division One Washington Road Princeton, New Jersey 08544 USA
200.43 linear feet
Morrison, Toni. 1931-
Consists of Toni Morrison's writings (manuscripts, drafts, galleys, and proofs), published books, working files, teaching files, correspondence, research files, press, photographs, awards, and memorabilia.
Consists of Toni Morrison's writings (manuscripts, drafts, galleys, etc.), published books, working files, teaching files, correspondence, research files, student papers, awards, interviews, press, and memorabilia.
Most of the collection is open for research. Toni Morrison's manuscript material, including drafts, typescripts, galleys, and proofs, are available only via digital access in the reading room.
Born-digital note TK.
Some material in this collection, particularly found in Series 1: Writings and Series 2: Correspondence, was damaged by the fire that destroyed Morrison's upstate New York home in 1993. Damage ranges from charred edges to pages missing significant portions or rendered illegible.
2009 (AM 2015-62). 2015 accruals: (AM 2015-74), (AM 2015-89), (AM 2015-98).
Morrison, Toni.; African American authors -- 20th century -- Sources.; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Sources.; Novelists.; Women Nobel Prize winners.; Correspondence.; Fan mail.; Interviews.; Proofs (printed matter).; Typescripts.
- Series 1: Writings, 1929 September-2015; 100 boxes (3 partial)
  Consists of research material, notes, outlines, drafts, galleys, and proofs. Yellow legal notepads contain notes, early draft material, and inserts for later typed and printed versions. Notepads are identified by their first lines, though a single notepad may contain a variety of material, including material relating to other works, correspondence drafts, and other unrelated notes. Corrected typescript and printout drafts often show significant revisions. Material from various stages of the publication process is present, including setting copies with copy-editor's and typesetter's marks, galleys, page proofs, F&Gs (folded and gathered pages not yet bound), blueline proofs ("confirmation blues"), advance copies (bound uncorrected proofs) and production/design material with page and dust-jacket samples.
  - Subseries 1: Novels, 1929 September-2015; 66 boxes (4 partial)
    Arranged chronologically by publication date.
    All of Morrison's novels except Song of Solomon are represented (this material was likely destroyed in the 1993 fire).
    - The Bluest Eye, 1970; 2 boxes
      For the short story "Two of Eves," an early version of The Bluest Eye, see Subseries 2: Short Fiction.
      - Outlines and Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Toni Morrison has required the Library to make surrogate copies of all of her manuscripts (including typescripts and proofs) and diaries (appointment books), including but not restricted to those damaged by fire in 1993. This is for conservation reasons, to prevent damage and deterioration by repeated use. Researchers are required to use digital surrogates in the reading room of the Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
      - "The Bluest Eye: On the southeast corner...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - "II. It would be inaccurate...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - "III. 3. This was at least the fifth time...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - "Notes for The Bluest Eye/Part IV Social worker: and Eunice", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - "At one time people only saw slow footed teenage boys...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - "Att: To Him Who Greatly Ennobled Human Nature...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - "Where's the mirror again?", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - "Cholly and the Block Boys...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - "Soaphead Church", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - "1. Rosemary Magazini is our friend...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - "We--Frieda And Me--Meet Eunice", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - "It was autumn when Mr. Shelby came...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - "'Let's do something' Frieda said.", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - "1. More on house: and life in it...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - "We dropped our seeds...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - "A Play", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Draft Fragments, undated; 1 folder Typescript, corrected. (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Typescript (original and photocopy), corrected. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Typescript (original and photocopy), corrected. (Box 1, Folder 22, Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders Typescript (original and photocopy), corrected. (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
      - Galley Proofs, 1970; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Sula, 1973; 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Draft Fragment, undated; 1 item Typescript, corrected. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Draft, 1973; 1 item Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Setting Copy, 1973; 1 item Typescript, corrected. (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Confirmation Blues, 1973 October 9; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Galley Proofs, 1973; 1 item (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Galley Proofs: Marked Set, 1973; 1 item (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Tar Baby, 1981-1983; 6 boxes (2 partial)
      - Notes, undated; 1 folder Typescript. (Box 6, Folder 1)
        One page, numbered 14.
      - Draft, undated; 4 folders Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 6, Folder 2-5)
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders Typescript, corrected. (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Typescript, corrected. (Box 8, Folder 1, Box 7, Folder 3-5)
      - Draft, undated; 2 folders Typescript, corrected. (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
      - Draft, undated; 1 folder Typescript, corrected. (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Advance Copy, 1981; 1 item (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Galley Proofs, 1981; 1 item (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Screenplay Draft, undated; 2 folders Typescript, corrected. (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
      - Screenplay Draft, 1983; 2 folders Typescript, corrected. (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
      - Screenplay Draft, undated; 2 folders Typescript. (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Beloved, 1984 September 21-1999; 8 boxes
      Numbered drafts per original folder labels.
      - Research Files, 13 folders
        - 19th Century Legislation Regarding Slaves, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - Atlanta Historical Society, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - Bibliographies, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - Blacks in Circuses, Slideshows, etc., undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Cincinnati (19th Century), undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - Database, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
        - Kentucky (19th Century), undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - Kentucky State Historical Society, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
        - Middle Passage, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous Research Findings (Copies), undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
        - Slave Narratives, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12, Folder 11)
        - Smith, James McCune, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
        - Sojourner Truth, undated; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Writing Schedule, undated; 1 item Typescript. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - House Sketch, undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Family Tree, undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Calendar, undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Outlines and Notes, undated; 1 item Typescript, corrected. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - "Hi Man had said...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - "TR to Stamp Paid", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - "After the ice skating", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - "Her father's daughter...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - "Denver who knew all about silence...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - "Some thoughts", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - "Curtains--light--humming", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - "6. JFK...", undated; 1 item Notepad. (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - "I don't have to explain...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - "124 was loud...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - "Denver comes out...", undated; 1 item Notepad pages. (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Draft Fragments, undated; 2 folders Typescript, corrected. (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
      - Synopsis and Early Draft, undated; 1 folder Typescript. (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Draft 1, undated; 1 item Typescript, corrected. (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Draft 2, undated; 1 item Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Draft 3, 1984 September 21; 1 item Typescript. (Box 14, Folder 1)
        With note from Mary Maguire.
      - Draft, undated; 1 item Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
      - Draft 6, undated; 1 item Typescript, corrected. (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
        Robert Gottlieb's copy.
      - Draft, undated; 1 item Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 15, Folder 1-4, Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Draft, undated; 1 item Typescript (photocopy), corrected. (Box 16, Folder 2-4, Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - Setting Copy, 1987; 1 item Typescript, corrected. (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
      - Author's Set Rough Pages, 1987; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      - First Pass Master Rough Pages, 1987; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
      - Master Page Proofs, 1987; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
      - Cut Page Proofs, 1987; 1 item (Box 18, Folder 7, Box 19, Folder 1)
      - First Pass Author's Set Proofs for Reprint, 1998; 1 item (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
      - Second Pass Proofs for Reprint, 1998; 1 item (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
      - Third Pass Proofs for Reprint, 1999; 1 item (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Jazz, 1929 September-1992; 10 boxes (2 partial)
      - Research Files, 1929 September-1992; 2 boxes (1 partial)
        - 1990 Research Assistant Notes, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - "African-American Properties Recognized in the National Register of Historic Places", undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Anderson, Jervis: This Was Harlem: A Cultural Portrait 1900-1950, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Andrews, Charles: "A History of the NY African Free Schools, 1787 to Present" (1830), undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 4)
          Photocopied excerpt of book, originally published in 1830, reprinted 1960 by Negro Universities Press.
        - Background Notes and Photocopies, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - "Blacks in Pennsylvania History" Afro-American Historical & Cultural Museum, Philadelphia, 1988; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - Bontemps, Anna: The Harlem Renaissance Remembered, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - Bulletin of NY Public Library "Ethiopia Unshackled", 1987; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 8)
          Photocopied journal article published April 1965.
        - Correspondence Related to Next Publication, 1987 December-1988 February; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Dixon, Robert: "The Education of the Negro in NYC 1853-1900", undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Fox, Ted: Showtime at the Apollo, "Harlem's Early Years--The Apollo's Heritage", undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - Franklin, Vincent: "The Education of Black Philadelphia, 1900-1950", undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 12)
          Photocopied excerpt of book, published in 1979 by the University of Pennsylvania Press.
        - Historical Society of Pennsylvania, 1988; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 13)
          Photocopied excerpt of book, originally published in 1868 by the Government Printing Office.
        - History of Schools for the Colored Population, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 14)
          Photocopied excerpt of book, published by Arno Press and the New York Times, 1969.
        - Huggins, Nathan: Harlem Renaissance, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 15)
          Photocopied excerpt of book, published by Oxford University Press, 1971.
        - Jones, Norrence: "Masters, Slaves, and Those Between: Controls and Controllers in Antebellum South Carolina", 1987; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 16)
        - Lewis, David Levering: When Harlem was in Vogue, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 17)
          Photocopied excerpt of book published by Knopf, 1981.
        - Mabee, Carleton: "Black Education in NY State: From Colonial to Modern Times", undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 18)
          Photocopied excerpt of book, published by Syracuse University Press, 1979.
        - McPherson, James M. "The Abolitionist Legacy: From Reconstruction to the NAACP", undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 19)
        - Ment, David: "Patterns of Public School Segregation, 1900-1940: Comparison of NYC, New Rochelle, & New Haven", undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 20)
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 21)
        - Negro Education: A Study of the Private and Higher Schools for Colored People in the US, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 22)
          Photocopied excerpt of book, published by Arno Press and New York Times, 1969.
        - The New York Age, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 23)
          Photocopied pages of newspapers dated 1917-1926.
        - The New York Amsterdam News, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 24)
          Photocopied pages of newspapers dated 1926.
        - Opportunity: "Negro Migration in NY State" & Misc. Other Articles, undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 1)
          Photocopied pages of newspapers dated January, 1926.
        - Opportunity: A Journal of Negro Life, undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 2)
          Photocopied pages of newspapers dated July and August, 1926.
        - Opportunity: A Journal of Negro Life, 1929 September; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Osofsky, Gilbert: Harlem: The Making of a Ghetto Negro New York 1890-1930, undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 4)
          Photocopied excerpt of book published by Harper & Row, 1966.
        - The Quaker Collection, Haverford College, undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 5)
          Photocopied document originally published 1897.
        - Research Materials, undated; 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
        - Research for Sequel to Beloved, 1987-1988; 3 folders (Box 21, Folder 8-10)
        - Schiffman, Jack: Harlem Heyday: A Pictoral History of Black Show Business and the Apollo, undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 11)
        - "Sugar Hill: A Citadel of Styles and Echoes of an Earlier America", undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 12)
          Photocopied article published 1987.
        - Survey Magazine, 1987; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 13)
          Photocopied pages of magazine published 1925.
        - Thompson, Marion: "The Education of Negroes in New Jersey" (1971), undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 14)
          Photocopied excerpt of book published by Arno Press and New York Times, 1971.
        - Walker, Sheila: "The Feast of Good Death: An Afro-Catholic Emancipation Celebration in Brazil", 1992; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 15)
          Photocopied article published in SAGE, Fall 1986.
        - The Weeksville Society, 1988; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 16)
        - Work, Monroe: "A Bibliography of the Negro in Africa & America", undated; 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 17)
          Photocopied excerpt of book published by Argosy-Antiquarian Inc., 1965.
      - Notes, 1989; 1 folder Autograph, typescript, and printouts, corrected. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Jazz Mss/Yellows, undated; 1 folder Notepads. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Jazz Miscellaneous 1, undated; 1 folder Autograph, typescript, and printouts, corrected. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Jazz Miscellaneous 2, 1990; 1 folder Printouts, corrected. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Jazz Manuscript Print [Early Draft], 1989; 1 folder Printouts, corrected. (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 1, 1989 June 23-1991 January 19; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - 1989 August 19, 1 item
          Pages 1-11.
        - 1990 September 23, 1 item
          Pages 1-20.
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 1-2.
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 1-29.
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 1-5.
        - J Inserts, undated; 1 item
          Pages 1-4.
        - Jopen, undated; 1 item
        - Jopen, undated; 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 1-30.
        - 1989 June 23, 1 item
          Pages 1-6.
        - 1989 June 23, 1 item
          Pages 1-27.
        - 1991 January 19, 1 item
          Pages 1-25.
        - 1989 July 11, 1 item
          Pages 1-7.
        - 1990 October 16, 1 item
        - 1989 December 25, 1 item
        - 1990 July 23, 1 item
          Pages 1-13.
        - 1991 January 19, 1 item
      - Chapter 2, 1990 July 5-1991 January 20; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - 1990 October 16, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - 1990 July 5, 1 item
          Pages 1-3.
        - 1990 July 19, 1 item
        - 1990 October 16, 1 item
        - 1991 January 20, 1 item
          Pages 1-33.
        - 1991 January 20, 1 item
      - Chapter 3, 1989 July 11-1991 February 22; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - 1991 January 21, 1 item
        - 1991 February 22, 1 item
          Pages 1-18.
        - 1990 October, 1 item
          Pages 1-21.
        - undated, 1 item
          2 pp.
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 26-41.
        - undated, 1 item
        - Alice Manfred, 1989 July 11; 1 item
          Page 1.
        - 1990 July 30, 1 item
          Pages 1-14 and inserts.
        - 1990 July 30, 1 item
          Pages 1-9.
        - 1990 October 31, 1 item
        - December 3, 1 item
          Pages 2-11.
        - 1990 July 30, 1 item
        - December 3, 1 item
        - 1991 January 6, 1 item
        - 1991 January 18, 1 item
        - 1991 January 18, 1 item
          Pages 1-17.
        - Insert, February 22; 1 item
      - Chapter 4, 1990 September 23-1991 January 21; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 1-35.
        - 1990 September 23, 1 item
        - Dorcus, undated; 1 item
          Pages 1-12.
        - Insert, undated; 1 item
          Pages 2-3.
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 1-10.
        - Jazzorg2, undated; 1 item
          Page 4.
        - Joe Trace, undated; 1 item
          3 pp.
        - Dorcus, undated; 1 item
        - Dorcus, undated; 1 item
        - 1990 November 23, 1 item
        - 1991 January 21, 1 item
          Pages 1-31.
        - 1991 January 21, 1 item
          Pages 1-26.
      - Chapter 5, 1990 July 22-1991 January 21; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 1-24.
        - 1990 July 22, 1 item
          Pages 1-19.
        - 1990 October, 1 item
          Pages 1-15.
        - 1990 November 2, 1 item
        - 1990 November 7, 1 item
          Pages 1-14.
        - 1990 November 30, 1 item
        - 1991 January 21, 1 item
      - Chapter 6, 1990 September 28-November 25; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - 1990 Summer, 1 item
        - 1990 September 28, 1 item
        - 1990 October 9, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
          Pages 2-30.
        - 1990 November 25, 1 item
      - Chapter 7, 1990 November 2-1991 January 20; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - undated, 1 item
        - 1990 November 2, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - 1990 November 20, 1 item
          Pages 1-16.
        - 1991 January 20, 1 item
          Pages 1-23.
      - Chapter 8, 1991 January 19-February 1; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - undated, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - undated, 1 item
        - 1991 January 19, 1 item
        - 1991 February 1, 1 item
      - Chapter 9, 1991 January 30-March 11; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - undated, 1 item
        - 1991 January 30, 1 item
        - 1991 March 11, 1 item
      - Jazz End, 1989 June 5-1991 January 19; 1 folder Corrected printouts in annotated folder. (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Chapter 10, undated; 1 item
        - Chapter 10, undated; 1 item
        - Jazz End Last Version, 1989 June 5; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1989 June 26; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1989 June 26; 1 item
          Pages 5-6.
        - Replace Jazz End, 1989 June 26; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 July 5; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 July 12; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 November 21; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 December 30; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1990 December 30; 1 item
        - Replace Jazz End, 1991 January 19; 1 item
      - "To see if we can write on this machine...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 10, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 7, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 7, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
        Page 226.
      - Golden Gray/Chapter 6, 1990 November 25; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
        Pages 1-22.
      - Chapter 4, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Notes: Chapter 3, 1991 February 22; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 5, 1990 November 30; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
        Page 18.
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 5, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - "It's hard figuring people out...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - J additions, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 7, 1991 January 20; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - "...sodden with liquid rage", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
        Pages 7-9.
      - Hunter, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 7, 1990 October; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Golden, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
        Pages 1-8.
      - Violet, 1989 July 11; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - "That's a thing to see...", undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Jazz/draft, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
        Pages 2-8.
      - Dorcus, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Violet/2, undated; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Violet/3 re: Golden Gray, 1989 July 14; portion of 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)